# Dan Ogrodnik

Dan.Ogrodnik@gmail.com www.DanOgrodnik.com

#### Profile:

Front-end Developer, Audio Engineer, former C-level executive of a multinational talent provider, and educator. Skills include HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Python, Ruby, and specializes in React. Prior experience in sales, fundraising, event production, staffing, and customer service. Classically trained musician with strong analysis and memorization skills, and ability to learn new systems quickly. Highly experienced in improvisation. Experienced with DAWs, audio engineering, recording, live sound, lighting, event production, streaming, management, and education K-12 undegrad and postgrad. Fluent in music theory and notation.

#### Education:

MFA, Music 2013 California Institute of the Arts, Valencia, CA BM, Music 2009 Hartt School of Music, University of Hartford, CT

## Current Occupations:

#### Staff Accompanist

USC Glorya Kaufman School of Dance 05/2016 - present

#### Web Developer

**Self-Employed** 05/2013 – present

#### Previous Experience:

## **Chief Operating Officer**

**Concert Talent** 07/2014 – 01/2017

- COO of a multinational talent provider handling large-scale event production
- Produced 350+ events in a 3-month period with MAC Cosmetics Magic of the Night campaign

## Faculty, Stage Production

AGBU Vatche and Tamar Manoukian High School 05/2017 – 08/2020

- Taught stage class for high schoolers including lights, live sound, recording, scenic design, stage management, concert production, woodworking, and more
- Audio, lighting, stage technician for independent events
- Ran an extracurricular music club with ensembles that performed live at Rose Bowl festivities

#### **Artist Department**

LA Philharmonic, Hollywood Bowl 05/2013 – 09/2015

- · Additional positions held with Ticket Sales and Fundraising
- · First and last point of contact between performing artists and the Los Angeles Philharmonic
- · Coordinated artist transportation to and from airports, hotels, rehearsals, performances, and more
- Performance equipment cartage